goodshop.com 2019-06-24

# Goodshop - privacy policy

#### Last Updated August 28, 2017

## WHAT THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVERS

Goodsearch (including the Goodsearch Search Engine and Goodshop), takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. This policy covers how Goodsearch treats personal information that Goodsearch collects and receives, including information related to your past use of Goodsearch products and services. This policy does not apply to the practices of our partners who help us provide some of the services offered through our Website (see below for additional information). Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable, like your name, address, photo, or email address, and that is not otherwise publicly available. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing your personal information with us.

## INFORMATION COLLECTION

#### General

GoodSearch collects limited non-personally identifying information and records information from your computer and browser, including your IP address, the date and time of your query, GoodSearch cookie information, software and hardware attributes, and the page you request. We use this information to operate, develop and improve our services.

#### Personal Information

The GoodSearch Search Engine do not require any personally identifiable information. However, if you opt to register and set up a personal account on GoodSearch, you will be asked to provide certain personally identifiable information. Your personally identifiable information is used to set up your GoodSearch account and to create your profile. Information on your profile is limited to your name, the organizations and causes you support, your actions, your amount raised and your list of friends; it does not include any other personally identifiable information such as your email or home address. By default, access to your profile is made public

## INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE

GoodSearch does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with GoodSearch under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help GoodSearch communicate with you about offers from GoodSearch and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of GoodSearch's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
  * We transfer information about you if GoodSearch is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, GoodSearch will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy

GoodSearch displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click targeted ads meet the targeting criteria—for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area.

  * GoodSearch does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad.
  * GoodSearch advertisers include financial service providers (such as banks, insurance agents, stock brokers and mortgage lenders) and non-financial companies (such as stores, airlines, and software companies).

GoodSearch works with vendors, partners, advertisers, and other service providers in different industries and categories of business.

## COOKIES

GoodSearch may set and access GoodSearch cookies on your computer.

Goodsearch may also use a Double-Click cookie to access non personally identifiable information via Google Analytics, such as Demographics and Interest Reporting. You can opt out of Google Analytics tracking for all websites by clicking here You can learn more about Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting here

GoodSearch lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to GoodSearch's cookies.

## Third Party Advertising Cookies

Some advertising partners may use cookies to provide advertising which is intended to be more relevant to you. This is done by understanding what may interest you based on your web browsing and web searches and placing a cookie on your device which can then be recognized on selected other websites. Advertising can then be displayed to you which corresponds better to the interests indicated by the information stored by that cookie.

No personal data is passed to our advertising partners and they cannot identify you or contact you directly. The cookies used for this purpose process only the search terms you use and technical information relating to your PC or other device as follows:

  * the referral search term (i.e., the term you entered into a search engine which then displayed our site as a search result);
  * the onsite search term (i.e., a term you entered in the search box on our site);
  * the type of internet browser you are using;
  * the operating system of your PC or other device;
  * the time and date you landed on or searched our site;
  * time spent on our webpage;
  * the address of the site which referred you to our site.

The partners we work with for these services are listed below and they have their own privacy statements which you should review:

  * Captify: <http://www.captify.co.uk/privacy-policy>

Controlling Use of Third Party Advertising Cookies You can prevent cookies being placed by particular advertising partners by visiting their websites referred to above, or the "Your Online Choices" page provided by the Interactive Advertising Bureau (IAB), that provides an easy way to prevent the use of advertising cookies from any or all of the advertising networks that are members of the IAB:  
<http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices>

 _Your web browser will also provide various settings which can be modified in order to delete particular cookies or to block all or specific third party cookies. Please bear in mind that a blocking cookie is used when you tell a particular company that you do not accept their advertising cookies so if you delete all your cookies you would have to repeat the process. Please note that deleting or blocking all cookies may make it impossible to login to or use many websites or at least some of their features_

## MISCELLANEOUS

You can edit or delete your nonprofit's account information and your email preferences, at any time.

New categories of marketing communications might be added from time to time. Users can opt out of receiving future marketing communications from these new categories or they can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages they receive.

We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the GoodSearch service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the GoodSearch Newsletter, that are considered part of your GoodSearch account, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them.

## CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.

## PUBLIC INFORMATION

Our website contains links to other websites available to you. You should carefully review the privacy policy posted by these websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. We also make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and news groups available to you. Please understand that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information. We have no control over its use and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

## CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

GoodSearch may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by placing a prominent notice on our site.

## CONTACT

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us at informati[[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or:

Privacy Matters  
c/o GoodSearch, LLC  
P.O. Box 492176  
Los Angeles, CA 90049  
415-610-8636
